Guide to the Barry Gifford Papers M0927
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Manuscripts
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves: [2 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
    TMsS with holographic notes, pp. 51-100
  - Landscape with Traveler: The Pillow Book of Francis Reeves: [3 of 3], undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    TMsS with holographic notes, pp. 101-154
  - Landscape with Traveler: "The Invitation", undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    TMs, 6 pp., ANS
  - "The Last Lunchcart Christmas, 1972 Dec 6 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    TMs, 6 pp., ANSTms, 3pp, 1 ANS
  - Letters to Proust, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Libretto for La Punaise, by Barry Gifford and Vinnie Deserio, 2 copies, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Living in Advance (with Paul de Barros and David Bromige) Rohnert Park, CA: Open Reading Books, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    songbook
  - The Lost Highway by David Lynch and Barry Gifford, First Draft [1 of 3], 1995, Apr 30 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Lost Highway by David Lynch and Barry Gifford, First Draft [2 of 3], 1995, Apr 30 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Lost Highway by David Lynch and Barry Gifford, First Draft [3of 3], 1995, Apr 30 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    TMs, pp. 101-114
  - The Lost Highway by David Lynch and Barry Gifford, Revised, 1995 Mar 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    TMsS, 14 pp.
  - Madrugada, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Madrugada, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    AMsS, 54 pp.
  - Montana Joe, First Draft [1 of 2], 1994 Dec 1 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Montana Joe, First Draft [2 of 2], 1994 Dec 1 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    TMs, pp. 51-97
  - Murder at the Swordfish Club, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Murder at the Swordfish Club: Research Materials: In the Land of the Long White Cloud [xerox; not written by Barry Gifford], undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Murder at the Swordfish Club: Research Materials, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Nadia in Paradise: Original Manuscript, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [1 of 7], undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [2 of 7], undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [3 of 7], undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [4 of 7], undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [5 of 7], undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [6 of 7], undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Naked Girl / La Jeune Fille Nue, by Francis Jammes, translated by Barry Gifford and Bettina Dickie [7 of 7], undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    TMs, 62 pp.
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of the Chicago Cubs: original manuscript [1 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of the Chicago Cubs: original manuscript [2 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of the Chicago Cubs: original manuscript [3 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of the Chicago Cubs: original manuscript [4 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of the Chicago Cubs: original manuscript [5 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    TMs, 49 pp.
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: typescript used for printing [1 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: typescript used for printing [2 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: typescript used for printing [3 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: typescript used for printing [4 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    TMs, pp. 151-200
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: typescript used for printing [5 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    TMs, pp. 201-227
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: Research materials [1 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: Research materials [2 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: Research materials [3 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: Research materials [4 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: Research materials [5 of 5], undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of Chicago and the Cubs [1 of 5], undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of Chicago and the Cubs [2 of 5], undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of Chicago and the Cubs [3 of 5], undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of Chicago and the Cubs [4 of 5], undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The Neighborhood of Baseball: A Personal History of Chicago and the Cubs [5 of 5], undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    TMs, pp. 201-244
  - New Mysteries of Paris, circa 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    TMs, 73 pp., 1 ALS
  - New Mysteries of Paris [1 of 2], undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - New Mysteries of Paris [2 of 2], undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    TMs, pp. 51-83
  - Night People: original manuscripts [front matter] [1 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Night People: original manuscripts [2 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Night People: original manuscripts [3 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    TMs, pp. 51-99
  - Night People: original manuscripts [4 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    TMs, pp. 100-150
  - Night People: original manuscripts [5 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    TMs, pp. 151-199
  - Night People: original manuscripts [6 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Night People: original manuscripts [7 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    AMs, 50 pp.
  - Night People: original manuscripts [8 of 8], undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    AMs, 49 pp.
  - Night People [1 of 4], undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    TMs, pp. i-viii, 1-50
  - Night People [2 of 4], undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Night People [3 of 4], undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Night People [4 of 4], undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - The North American Indian: Selected Writings of Edward S. Curtis [1 of 5], undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    TMs, 8 pp
  - The North American Indian: Selected Writings of Edward S. Curtis [2 of 5], undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    TMs, 50 pp
  - The North American Indian: Selected Writings of Edward S. Curtis [3 of 5], undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - The North American Indian: Selected Writings of Edward S. Curtis [4 of 5], undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The North American Indian: Selected Writings of Edward S. Curtis [5 of 5], undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    TMs, 14 pp
  - A Note on Inspiration and Other Poems, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Notes From A Room With A View [2 copies], undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    TMs, 11 pp., TM, 1 p
  - "O Fly" [sheet music], undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - On the Road: A Treatment by Barry Gifford, 1994 Feb 27 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    TMsS, 23 pp.
  - On the Road: Screenplay: First Draft [1 of 2], 1994 May 30 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    TMsS, pp. 1-50
  - On the Road: Screenplay: First Draft [2 of 2], 1994 May 30 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    TMsS, pp. 51-107
  - On the Road: Screenplay: Second Draft [1 of 2], 1994 Aug 23 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    TMs, pp. 1-55
  - On the Road: Screenplay: Second Draft [2 of 2], 1994 Aug 23 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    TMs, pp. 56-117
  - Out of the Past: A Personal Portrait of Key West, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    TMs with holographic notes, 14 pp.
  - Perdita Durango: A Screenplay [Based on 59º and Raining: The Story of Perdita Durango]: Second Revised Draft [1 of 2], 1993 Aug 16 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    TMsS, 50 pp
  - Perdita Durango: A Screenplay [Based on 59º and Raining: The Story of Perdita Durango]: Second Revised Draft [2 of 2], 1993 Aug 16 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    TMsS, 59 pp
  - Perdita Durango: A Screenplay [Based on 59º and Raining: The Story of Perdita Durango]: First Revised Draft [1 of 3], 1993 May (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Perdita Durango: A Screenplay [Based on 59º and Raining: The Story of Perdita Durango]: First Revised Draft [2 of 3], 1993 May (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Perdita Durango: A Screenplay [Based on 59º and Raining: The Story of Perdita Durango]: First Revised Draft [3 of 3], 1993 May (Box 25, Folder 2)
    TMsS, 20 pp.
  - Perdita Durango [1 of 4], undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Perdita Durango [2 of 4], undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Perdita Durango [3 of 4], undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Perdita Durango [4 of 4], undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    TMs, pp. 151-179
  - Perdita Durango [1 of 3], 1996 June 23 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Perdita Durango [2 of 3], 1996 June 23 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Perdita Durango [3 of 3], 1996 June 23 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    TMs, pp. 101-127
  - Persimmons: Poems for Paintings, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Phantom Father: Correspondence with Walter Bode, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - The Phantom Father: Barry Gifford's Rough Guide, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - The Phantom Father: "The Mystery", undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    TMs with holographic revisions, 1 p.
  - The Phantom Father: "Listening to the News", undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    TMs with holographic revisions, 2 pp.
  - The Phantom Father: "Foreword", undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - The Phantom Father: "The Trophy", undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    AMs, 6 pp.
  - The Phantom Father: "The Getaway", undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The Phantom Father: "The Getaway", undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The Phantom Father: "The Mystery", undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    TMs with holographic revisions and AMs, 2 pp.
  - The Phantom Father: "Kid who Torched the Charterhouse of Parma" [2 copies], undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - The Phantom Father: "The Trophy", undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    TMs, 5 pp.
  - The Phantom Father: "Coda", undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    TMs, 1 p. with photocophy
  - The Phantom Father, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    TMs and 1 TLS
  - The Phantom Father, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - The Phantom Father: publication announcement, Harcourt Brace & Co., 1997 Spring-Summer (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Phantom Father: galley proofs with holographic revisions [1 of 5], undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    TMs, a-b; i-xiv, 1-50
  - The Phantom Father: galley proofs with holographic revisions [2 of 5], undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    TMs, pp 51-100
  - The Phantom Father: galley proofs with holographic revisions [3 of 5], undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    TMs, pp 101-150
  - The Phantom Father: galley proofs with holographic revisions [4 of 5], undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    TMs, pp 151-201
  - The Phantom Father: galley proofs with holographic revisions [5 of 5], undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    TMs, pp 202-262
  - The Pilkington/Gifford Letters [Star Route Press], 1970 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    TMs, 17 pp
  - The Pilkington/Gifford Letters ... 1 July 1969- 28 April 1971: A Supplement... [Madrugada Press] (Box 26, Folder 8)
    TMs, 10 pp
  - Poems, undated c 1973? (Box 26, Folder 9)
    AMs, 9 pp.
  - Poems From Snail Hut, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Poems From Snail Hut: original manuscript, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Port Tropique: Proposal for Television Series, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    TMs, 1 p. with holographic notes
  - Port Tropique, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    TMs, 54 pp.
  - Port Tropique: Original Manuscript [1 of 4], undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Port Tropique: Original Manuscript [2 of 4], undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Port Tropique: Original Manuscript [3 of 4], undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Port Tropique: Original Manuscript [4 of 4], undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    TMs, 41 pp.
  - The Prayer of the Star Route, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - A Quinzaine in Return for a Portrait of Mary Sun, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - A Quinzaine in Return for a Portrait of Mary Sun, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - A Quinzaine in Return for a Portrait of Mary Sun: Galley Proofs, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    20 pp.
  - Review of Shabegok and How the World Was Made [3 copies], Western American Literature, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Sailor's Holiday [1 of 3], undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Sailor's Holiday [2 of 3], undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    TMs, 56 pp.
  - Sailor's Holiday [3 of 3], undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    TMs, 70 pp.
  - Sailor's Holiday [1 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    TMs, pp. i-v, 1-50
  - Sailor's Holiday [2 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sailor's Holiday [3 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sailor's Holiday [4 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sailor's Holiday [5 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    TMs, pp. 201-250
  - Sailor's Holiday [6 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    TMs, pp. 251-300
  - Sailor's Holiday [7 of 7], undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    TMs, pp. 301-351
  - Sailor's Holiday [1 of 2], undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    2 TMs (1 p), TMs, pp. 1-39
  - Sailor's Holiday [2 of 2], undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    TMs, pp. 40-76
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [1 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [2 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [3 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [4 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [5 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [6 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [7 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [8 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [9 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Saroyan: A Biography by Lawrence Lee and Barry Gifford: xerox of typescript [10 of 10], circa 1984 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Saroyan: A Biography: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Saroyan: A Biography: Research Materials, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Saroyan: A Biography: Publicity, circa 1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Saroyan: A Biography [1 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    TMs, iii, pp. 1-51
  - Saroyan: A Biography [2 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    TMs, pp. 52-100
  - Saroyan: A Biography [3 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Saroyan: A Biography [4 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Saroyan: A Biography [5 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Saroyan: A Biography [6 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Saroyan: A Biography [7 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    TMs, pp. 301-350
  - Saroyan: A Biography [8 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    TMs, pp. 351-400
  - Saroyan: A Biography [9 of 9], undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    TMs, pp. 401-428
  - See You at Sundown, Harvard, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Selected Poems of Frances Jammes, 1976 July 14 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    photography and 1 TLs
  - Smart Mouth, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    TMs 5 pp with holographic notes; AM, 1 p
  - The State of Florida: Prospectus for the book, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    TMs 5 pp with holographic notes
  - The State of Florida: Prospectus for the proposed book, undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
    TMs with holographic notes
  - The State of Florida: Letter from Ann Godoff, editor at Atlantic Monthly Press, 1987 Oct 9 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    TMsS 1 p
  - The State of Florida: Letter fromStephen Drachman with contract for book, 1987 Nov 30 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    TLS -28 pp.
  - The State of Florida: Research Materials, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - The State of Florida: Research Materials, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Jay Johnson, NOA, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    TMs 6 pp
  - The State of Florida: Letter to Ann Godoff, editor at Atlantic Monthly re. book proposal, 1987 May 8 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    TMs 3 pp. with holographic notes
  - The State of Florida: Research Materials, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - The State of Florida: Research Materials: Articles and correspondence about fishing, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - The State of Florida: Research Materials, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Elwood Harry, Vic Dunaway, Greg McIntosh, Clint Allen and Rick Allen, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    TMs, 56 pp
  - The State of Florida: research materials, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - The State of Florida: Interview with E.K. Harry & Mike Leech, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Ross Davey, 1988 April 28 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Greg McIntosh, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Shaughan Anderson, 1988 Apr 28 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Tms, 10 pp
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Allen Merritt, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    TMs, 40 pp.
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Sandy Storer and Jack Colman [1 of 2], undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    TMs, pp. 1-33
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Sandy Storer and Jack Colman [2 of 2], undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    TMs, pp. 34-66
  - The State of Florida: Interview with Charlie Wheeland and Allen Merritt, 1988 Feb 9 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    TMs 26 pp
  - The Straight Man (By Pennifield Jensen & Barry Gifford) [Screenplay], undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    TMs, 85 pp
  - The Straight Man: scene inserts, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    TMs 34 pp.
  - The Straight Man: correspondence from Pennfield Jensen, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    1 TL, 1 TLS (2 pp)
  - The Straight Man: contracts, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    1 ALS, ! TL (2 pp), 1 TL (5 pp)
  - The Straight Man: Treatment, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    TMs, 16 pp
  - The Straight Man, with Pennfield Jensen: script [1 of 2], undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
    TMs, pp. 1-53
  - The Straight Man, with Pennfield Jensen: script [2 of 2], undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    TMs, pp. 54-106
  - The Straight Man, with Pennfield Jensen: script breakdown, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Sultans of Africa: First Draft [1 of 2], 1995 June 9 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Sultans of Africa: First Draft [2 of 2], 1995 June 9 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    TMs, pp. 51-103
  - Sultans of Africa: Treatment, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Sultans of Africa: Treatment, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Sultans of Africa [1 of 4], undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    TMs 51 pp.
  - Sultans of Africa [2 of 4], undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    TMs 54 pp.
  - Sultans of Africa [3 of 4], undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    AMs 49 pp.
  - Sultans of Africa [4 of 4], undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    AMs 28 pp.
  - That Night in the Cherokee, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    TMs 14 pp
  - That Night in the Cherokee, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    TMs 16 pp with holographic notes
  - They Don't Dance Much: Proposed Covers for screenplay, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    4 pp.
  - They Don't Dance Much: Revised 2nd Draft [1 of 2], 1992 Nov (Box 30, Folder 14)
    TMs, pp. 1-46
  - They Don't Dance Much: Revised 2nd Draft [2 of 2], 1992 Nov (Box 30, Folder 15)
    TMs, pp. 47-92
  - They Don't Dance Much: Revised 2nd Draft [1 of 2], 1992 Nov (Box 30, Folder 16)
    TMs with holographic notes, pp. 1-47
  - They Don't Dance Much: Revised 2nd Draft [2 of 2], 1992 Nov (Box 30, Folder 17)
    TMs with holographic notes, pp. 48-92
  - They Don't Dance Much [The Cry of the Mute, a screenplay by Pace Roscoe Ripley [1 of 2], undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    TMs pp. 1-45
  - They Don't Dance Much [The Cry of the Mute, a screenplay by Pace Roscoe Ripley [2 of 2], undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    TMs pp. 46-93
  - They Don't Dance Much: correspondence from American Playhouse, 1993 Mar 2 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    TLs, 2 pp.
  - They Don't Dance Much: correspondence: copies of letters to David Lynch, undated, 1992 Dec 9 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    1 TL, 1 TLS, 2 pp.
  - They Don't Dance Much [Coming Through Corinth]: deleted pages, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
    TMs with holographic notes 17 pp.
  - They Don't Dance Much [Coming Through Corinth]: revised draft [1 of 2], undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
    TMs with holographic notes pp. 1-45
  - They Don't Dance Much [Coming Through Corinth]: revised draft [2 of 2], undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    TMs with holographic notes pp. 46-89
  - They Don't Dance Much [Coming Through Corinth]: revised draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    TMs with holographic notes 57 pp.
  - They Don't Dance Much: photocopy of typescript from Propaganda Films [1 of 3], undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - They Don't Dance Much: photocopy of typescript from Propaganda Films [2 of 3], undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    TMs with holographic notes pp. 46-90
  - They Don't Dance Much: photocopy of typescript from Propaganda Films [3 of 3], undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    TMs with holographic notes pp. 91-128
  - They Don't Dance Much: holographic treatment, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    TMs with AMs 5 pp
  - To My Muse [sheet music], undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - The Tunisian Notebook: original manuscript, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    TMs, 33 pp.
  - Twelfth Street [croadside card], circa 1977 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Uncle Buck (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Tms, 14 pp.
  - An Unfortunate Woman: original manuscript [1 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - An Unfortunate Woman: original manuscript [2 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - An Unfortunate Woman: original manuscript [3 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - An Unfortunate Woman: original manuscript [4 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 14)
    TMs, pp. 151-194
  - An Unfortunate Woman: final galley proofs [front matter] [1 of 5] (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - An Unfortunate Woman: final galley proofs [2 of 5] (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - An Unfortunate Woman: final galley proofs [3 of 5] (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - An Unfortunate Woman: final galley proofs [4 of 5] (Box 31, Folder 18)
    TMs, pp. 101-117
  - An Unfortunate Woman: final galley proofs [5 of 5] (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula [1 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 20)
    TMs, 59 pp.
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula [2 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula [3 of 4] (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula [4 of 4] (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula: final manuscript [1 of 4] (Box 32, Folder 2)
    TMs, 58 pp.
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula: final manuscript [2 of 4] (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula: final manuscript [3 of 4] (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Wild at Heart: The Story of Sailor and Lula: final manuscript [4 of 4] (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Wild at Heart [screenplay by David Lynch] [1 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Wild at Heart [screenplay by David Lynch] [2 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Wild at Heart [screenplay by David Lynch] [3 of 3] (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Wild at Heart [screenplay by David Lynch]: First Draft [1 of 3], 1989 June 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Wild at Heart [screenplay by David Lynch]: First Draft [2 of 3], 1989 June 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Wild at Heart [screenplay by David Lynch]: First Draft [3 of 3], 1989 June 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    TMs, pp.101-134